Pelke, Bill; Papers apap205
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Activism, 1984-2000, Undated; 6; 5.08 cubic feet
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 45)
  - Peace CENTER, 1997-1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 46)
  - Peace on Earth News, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 47)
  - Peacework, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 48)
  - Pennsylvania Abolitionists United Agasint the Death Penalty, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 49)
  - Pennsylvania Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 50)
  - People Against Racist Terror -Turning the Tide, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 51)
  - People of Faith Against the Death Penalty -Take Actions Not Lives, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 52)
  - The Phoenix, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 53)
  - Pilgrimage Peace and Justice Center -Pilgrimage News, 1990 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 54)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1990 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 55)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 56)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 57)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 58)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 59)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 60)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 61)
  - Prison Legal News, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 62)
  - Prison Legal News, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 63)
  - Prisoner and Community Together (PACT), 1993; 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 64)
  - Prisoner and Community Together -PACT Newsletter, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 65)
  - Prisoner and Community Together -PACT Newsletter, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 66)
  - The Prisoner 's Advocate Newsletter, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 67)
  - Project Hope, 1990; 1992; 1997; Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 68)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 69)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 70)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 71)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 72)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 73)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 74)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 75)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 76)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 77)
  - Quixote Center, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 78)
  - Quixote Center, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 79)
  - Quixote Center, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 80)
  - Quixote Center, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 81)
  - Quixote Center, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 82)
  - Quixote Center, 1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 83)
  - Quixote Center, Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 84)
  - The Radical Party, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 85)
  - Religion and the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 86)
  - Resist, 1992 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 87)
  - Resist, 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 88)
  - Resist, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 89)
  - Resist, 1995 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 90)
  - Resist, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 91)
  - Resist, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 92)
  - Resist, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 93)
  - Resist, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 94)
  - Resist, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 95)
  - Resist, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 96)
  - Resist, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 97)
  - Resist, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 98)
  - Resist, 1998 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 99)
  - Resist, 1999 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 100)
  - Rethinking Prisons, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 101)
  - Revolutionary Communist Party, U.S.A.Revolutionary Worker, 1997 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 102)
  - The Rising Sun, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 103)
  - Robert West Defense Fund, Undated (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 104)
  - Rock and Rap Confidential, 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Activism), Folder 105)
  - Rural Southern Voice for Peace -Voices, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - The Safer Society Press - Catalog, 1999 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - Save Our Sons and Daughters, 1990; 1997 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - Seamless Garment Network, 1993-1999 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - SOLPAE, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - SOLPAE -In Solidarity, 1993 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - SOLPAE -In Solidarity, 1994 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - SOLPAE -In Solidarity, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - SOLPAE -In Solidarity, 1996 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights -Human Rights Report, 1999 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1989; 1992; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - The Southern Poverty Law Center, Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - Stop the Executions of People, Inc., 1992; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - Symposium: Are Executions in New York Inevitable?, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - Tennessee Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1994 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - Tennessee Coalition to Abolish State Killing (TCASK), 1997; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - Texans Against State Killing, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
  - Texas Abolition Network, 1993; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 18)
  - Texas Abolition Network -The Network News, 1992 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 19)
  - Texas Abolition Network -The Network News, 1993 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 20)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 21)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 22)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 23)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 24)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 25)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 26)
  - Texas Alliance for Human Needs - Newsletters, 1998 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 27)
  - Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 28)
  - The Texas Observer, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 29)
  - Transnational, 1994; 1996 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 30)
  - Tree of Life Campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 31)
  - Unitarian Universalists Against the Death Penalty -Witness for Life, 1998 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 32)
  - United Farm Workers -Food Justice, 1994 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 33)
  - United Farm Workers -Food Justice, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 34)
  - United Steelworkers of America -The Organizer, 1991 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 35)
  - United Steelworkers of America -The Organizer, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 36)
  - United Steelworkers of America -The Organizer, 1998 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 37)
  - Unity Day - Button, 1994 (Oversize 5, Item 16)
  - Unity Day Project, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 38)
  - Victim Offender Reconciliation Program, 1993; Undated (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 39)
  - Victim Offender Services -Gatherings, 1995 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 40)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1988; 1990-1993 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 41)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons - 1992 Program Report, circa 1993 (Box 5 (6-General Activism), Folder 42)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to State Killing, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 1)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP), 1996-1997; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 2)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty -VADP Action, 1995 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 3)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty -VADP Action, 1996 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 4)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty -VADP Action, 1997 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 5)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty -VADP Action, 1998 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 6)
  - Voices for the Condemned Newsletter, 1995; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 7)
  - Voices from the Inside - Church of the Covenant: Unconditional Pardon, 1992 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 8)
  - War Resisters League, 1990; 1995-1996 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 9)
  - Washington Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers, 1994 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 10)
  - Western Missouri Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 11)
  - Wisconsin CURE, 1994; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 12)
  - Why do we kill people - Button, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 15)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1988 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 13)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1989 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 14)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1994 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 15)
  - Workers World, 1988 (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 16)
  - World Congress on Forgiveness - Jerusalem 2000, 1997; Undated (Box 6 (6-General Activism), Folder 17)
- Subject Files, 1965-1999, Undated; 7; 2.25 cubic feet
  This series contains biographical material related to Bill Pelke, reference material on the capital punishment, photographs, draft and non-published articles, religious materials, and poetry, songs, plays, and other artistic materials created by death row inmates or about the death penalty collected by Bill Pelke.
  - Abolition Day speech, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Address Given by Marie Deans, 1986 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Janey Appleseed - Draft Article, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Article from Death Row, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Artistic Works, 1983; 1991; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - " Better Off Dead " - T.V. movie, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Biddle Publishing - Frontiers of Justice, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Ariel Brugger, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - E.L. Brugan - Turner- articles, 1990; 1994 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Robin Casarjian - draft articles, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Child's Drawings, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Ashanti Chimurenga - First Draft Proposal, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Paula Cooper - Disciplinary Hearing, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Death Penalty Petition, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Grim Reaper Decoration, Undated (Oversized 6, Item 1)
  - House Bill 1802, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Humor, 1994; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Mary Hutchinson - Declaration of Life, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - In Your Hands - Community Action Guide for Human Rights Year and Beyond, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - International Court of Justice, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Earnest James Jr. - " Where do I Sign ", Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Charlie King - concert, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Morris Family News, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - "Not in My Name" - Rubber Stamp, Undated (Oversize 5, Item 6)
  - Bill Pelke Articles, 1992; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Bill Pelke - Biographical Materials, 1965; 1977; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Bill Pelke - Calendar, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Bill Pelke - Calendars, May-December, 1994 (Flat-file 1)
  - Bill Pelke - Calendars, 1995 (Flat-file 2)
  - Bill Pelke - Calendars, August-September, 1997 (Flat-file 3)
  - Bill Pelke - grandmother, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Bill Pelke - Italy trip, 1988 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Bill Pelke - name tags, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Bill Pelke - notes, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Bill Pelke - notes, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Bill Pelke - notes, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Bill Pelke - Washington D.C., Demonstration Arrest and Trial, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Bill Pelker - web searchers, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Pending Execution of William Andrews, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Phillipine Focus, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Michael John Poirier, 1993-1997 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Punching Nun Puppet, Undated (Oversized 4, Item 1)
  - Lisa Radelet - Report on Consensual Executions, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Reference Material, 1990-1998; Undated (Oversized 7, Folder 12)
  - Reference Material, 1990-1998; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Reference Material, 1990-1998; Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Reference Material, 1990-1998; Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Religious Material, 1987; 1990-1999; Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Religious Material, 1987; 1990-1999; Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Irene Rosenfeld - resume, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Michael Ross - draft articles, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - State of Ohio v. Ediberto Huertas, 1990 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - The State of Texas v. Robert Wallace West, Jr., 1994 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Synopsis of Human Rights Violations and Official Misconduct at Allen County Jail, 1995 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Teresa Newsletter #9, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Tim Robbins - interview, 1996 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Unknown Articles, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Unknown Conference Call, November 17, 1996 (Oversize 9, Cassette 3)
  - Unlabed, Undated (Oversize 9, 5.25in-floppy 2)
  - Unlabed, Undated (Oversize 9, Microcassette 1)
  - William Andrew's Statements, 1992 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Works - WS-Abuse, Jan, Undated (Oversize 9, 5.25in-floppy 1)